[
  {
    "question": "Leben",
    "answer": "ζωή",
    "phonetic": "zo**Í**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wort / Lehre",
    "answer": "λόγος",
    "phonetic": "**LÓ**gos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gott",
    "answer": "Θεός",
    "phonetic": "The**Ó**s"
  },
  {
    "question": "Freund",
    "answer": "φίλος",
    "phonetic": "**FÍ**los"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stern",
    "answer": "αστέρι",
    "phonetic": "a**STÉ**ri"
  },
  {
    "question": "Erde",
    "answer": "γη",
    "phonetic": "yi"
  },
  {
    "question": "Schreiben",
    "answer": "γράφω",
    "phonetic": "**GRÁ**fo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zeit",
    "answer": "χρόνος",
    "phonetic": "**CHRÓ**nos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mensch",
    "answer": "άνθρωπος",
    "phonetic": "**ÁN**thropos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Angst",
    "answer": "φόβος",
    "phonetic": "**FÓ**vos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kraft",
    "answer": "δύναμη",
    "phonetic": "**DÝ**nami"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wasser",
    "answer": "νερό",
    "phonetic": "ne**RÓ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Feuer",
    "answer": "φωτιά",
    "phonetic": "fo**TIÁ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Seele",
    "answer": "ψυχή",
    "phonetic": "psi**CHÍ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Licht",
    "answer": "φως",
    "phonetic": "fos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wissen",
    "answer": "γνώση",
    "phonetic": "**GNÓ**si"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kind",
    "answer": "παιδί",
    "phonetic": "pe**DÍ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tier",
    "answer": "ζώο",
    "phonetic": "**ZÓ**o"
  },
  {
    "question": "Welt",
    "answer": "κόσμος",
    "phonetic": "**KÓS**mos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Form",
    "answer": "μορφή",
    "phonetic": "mor**FÍ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sprache",
    "answer": "γλώσσα",
    "phonetic": "**GLÓ**ssa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Schule",
    "answer": "σχολείο",
    "phonetic": "scho**LÍ**o"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stimme",
    "answer": "φωνή",
    "phonetic": "fo**NÍ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tod",
    "answer": "θάνατος",
    "phonetic": "**THÁ**natos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Luft",
    "answer": "αέρας",
    "phonetic": "a**É**ras"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bewegung",
    "answer": "κίνηση",
    "phonetic": "**KÍ**nisi"
  },
  {
    "question": "Sehen",
    "answer": "βλέπω",
    "phonetic": "**VLÉ**po"
  },
  {
    "question": "Bild",
    "answer": "εικόνα",
    "phonetic": "i**KÓ**na"
  },
  {
    "question": "Wärme",
    "answer": "ζέστη",
    "phonetic": "**ZÉ**sti"
  },
  {
    "question": "Urteil",
    "answer": "κρίση",
    "phonetic": "**KRÍ**si"
  },
  {
    "question": "Energie",
    "answer": "ενέργεια",
    "phonetic": "e**NÉR**yeia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Feind",
    "answer": "εχθρός",
    "phonetic": "ech**THRÓS**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Körper",
    "answer": "σώμα",
    "phonetic": "**SÓ**ma"
  },
  {
    "question": "Herz",
    "answer": "καρδιά",
    "phonetic": "kar**DIÁ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "Gehirn",
    "answer": "εγκέφαλος",
    "phonetic": "en**GÉ**falos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Lärm",
    "answer": "θόρυβος",
    "phonetic": "**THÓ**ryvos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Buch",
    "answer": "βιβλίο",
    "phonetic": "vi**VLÍ**o"
  },
  {
    "question": "Stadt",
    "answer": "πόλη",
    "phonetic": "**PÓ**li"
  },
  {
    "question": "Zentrum",
    "answer": "κέντρο",
    "phonetic": "**KÉN**tro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Farbe",
    "answer": "χρώμα",
    "phonetic": "**CHRÓ**ma"
  }
]